

# Graphic Design + Marketing Specialist

# Jenna Howard

- j.m.howard30@gmail.com
- Macon, GA
- jhoward.design
- **(**478) 719-0474

## **Profile**

With 10 years in digital & traditional design, I specialize in turning ideas into powerful visual content. My expertise includes brand awareness, visual storytelling, graphic design, & client engagement. I've served a range of clients, ensuring each brand's voice resonates with their target.

#### **Skills**

- O PowerPoint
- FIGMA
- MailChimp
- Adobe Photoshop
- Facebook
- Adobe Illustrator
- Google Ads + Analytics
- Adobe PremierePro

# **Employment**

# 2020 - now Marketing Specialist at SPINEN

Collaborated with internal and client teams to craft visual designs for marketing materials and digital campaigns. Produced email campaigns that generated over \$30k in revenue. Managed social media and client engagement. Ensured brand consistency.

# 2019 - now Freelance Graphic Designer

Overhauled client branding & content planning. Developed & maintained client websites, Google Business pages, & social media accounts. Started mailing list for customer newsletters. Produced brochures, menus, photo shoots, signage, & digital advertising. Reported and presented client analytics.

#### 2018 - 2019 Project Manager at Third Wave Digital

Administered projects for national & small business campaigns. Executed complex digital communications on behalf of key clients (e.g. 7-Eleven) including 3rd party vendors. Maintained a visual matrix of both content & format variations for menu boards across region, store types, & times of day for >200 stores.

## Education

# 2011 - 2015 Georgia College & State University

Bachelor of Arts in Mass Communication